Subs Edited by DizzyAngelDemon...
made to fit the Uncut,
Directors Cut Edition of KITE in HD
Available at hshare.net
How do you like this building?
Is this a cool place or what?
Yeah...
You're special, you know.
Those ugly dogs in my fan
club don't know about this place.
You're disgusting, you vulgar,
arrogant, retarded celebrity punk...
Just because you have some TV show.
Give me a break.
Who do you think you are?
Shame--
You bitch!
How do you like being kicked
by a retarded celebrity punk?
You old bitch!
Your stinking perfume makes me sick!
You're the disgusting one, bitch!
I'm going to sue you for this...
M-My son is an excellent lawyer.
A punk like you will
be squashed like a bug.
Do you hear me, punk?
We found traces of two bullets...
in the chest and in the head.
I see signs of blood under the skin.
He must have died instantly.
Mr. Akai...
It must have been a very special gun...
The bullets exploded inside his body.
Better check those bullet fragments.
Is the medical team here yet?
They're all in the hospital
because of food poisoning.
Those assholes.
What a waste of our tax money.
What's with granny?
Probably shocked to death.
Looks like it was a heart attack.
Get an autopsy just in case.
So, this guy's a celebrity?
He has seven TV shows a week.
He's a popular comedian.
What a joke.
His usual material is about corpses.
Nobody's gonna laugh at this.
What a tearjerker.
H-He was such a nice guy.
W-Why would anyone kill him?
He was the nicest guy I ever knew.
I can't stand breaking
up our team like this...
Mr. Ogata at the studio?
His outraged fans are
rushing to the location.
We can see how popular he was...
Also, according to our sources,
this case may involve organized crime...
Well done.
I feel sorry for that old lady.
People die everyday.
Come here.
I'm not in the mood today.
Give it to me.
I know...
But...
Sawa...
I have enough problems already.
Anything wrong?
Can't you feel it?
Get on top.
Be more punctual, Oburi.
Who are we doing?
Which one?
All of them.
We've called someone else in.
You take care of the one in front.
The other one will take care of the rest.
What did they do?
The three of them are child molesters.
They're going to pay for what they did.
There's another one besides me...
How about this weekend again?
Call me when you can.
You know our usual activity...
My wife just isn't
good enough, you know?
Surprised?
You did it?
Right.
The reward for each
adult is the same as always.
Take it from Kanie later.
You stink, Mr. Akai.
Oburi, I don't have
an easy job, you know.
The stink from the corpses
makes my eyes water all the time.
And that rotten smell is so strong...
It's no wonder I always stink.
Mr. Akai...
Did you think about what I asked you?
Sure.
I don't want to hold you back.
Wow...
Your generosity makes me feel weird.
However...
...you have to take
care of three more jobs.
I knew you'd say that.
It's between you and me, isn't it?
We've got to be fair to each other.
Right, Kanie?
Isn't that right?
Mr. Kanie, I'll do my best to be on time.
What are you doing?
You suck!
You're so slow!
You retard!
Give it to me!
Hey, buddy, give us the ball!
You got my jacket dirty.
It wasn't that nice, anyway.
Go home and wash it yourself, okay?
He's pretty good.
That's why I need you.
1 05 yen is your change.
Thank you very much.
Hey!
You look good in that uniform.
You...
Tastes good.
This must be a new flavor.
Want some?
You asked Kanie
where I worked part-time?
So...
What?
Tell me your name.
Sawa.
As in ''the sand you can't hold''
and ''the feather blown by the wind.''
Remember that.
Is that your real name?
Of course.
I'm...
Oburi.
You're Oburi, right?
How much do you know about me?
Are you mad?
No, I'm just...
Kanie told me your name, that's all.
Is Oburi your real name?
Yeah, it is.
It's a very unusual name.
Everyone says that.
Do you have a family?
Nope.
You?
Me neither.
We're alike, aren't we?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Anything.
I'll tell you.
What is Akai to you?
He's...
...my guardian.
Same as me, huh?
What a strange coincidence...
...we have here.
Those earrings
must be very special to you.
Why's that?
You were wearing
them the last time, too.
They look weird, yet really beautiful.
They're...
...made from the
blood of my papa and mama.
It's kind of my lucky charm.
Let's go!
Where is it?
Your place.
Shit...
That's...
You know him?
He's a Hollywood movie star, isn't he?
Some of my classmates are fans.
But I didn't know that
he had a twin brother.
They'll be here in a few minutes.
This is the third celebrity.
Kill...
...the right one.
If I get the wrong one, I'm sorry.
He has three bodyguards, so be careful.
Where do I get him?
Give it back!
Give it back to me!
Don't you want to be
with your papa and mama?
Kill him.
This guy's one of the most
wanted, murdering, perverted bastards.
He's been kidnapping
young girls, raping them...
...and killing them by
chopping their bodies into pieces.
Who cares if one or
two guys like him die?
Find whoever killed my papa and mama.
Yeah, I swear I will.
Just die already!
Manager, someone may catch us!
Yes, but it's so exciting!
If we're lucky, we'll find
something left behind by the suspect.
Search every square inch of the room!
You think we can find
anything in this mess?
That's what a professional does, right?
If you fell from this height, it'd
be impossible to identify the body .
Lucky girl.
Must've grown wings or something.
Mr. Akai, can we come in now?
Yeah, go ahead.
There aren't that many
press people here today.
They're all at the police station.
Did they find out about the
chief's Lolita complex or something?
Huh? You didn't know?
There's a witness!
What?
Did he say anything?
No.
He's still in shock, but...
...it's a woman.
A woman?
The killer was a woman.
A young one.
Mr. Akai...
...how long
have you been there?
Kanie, your woman
may have to wait a while.
I'm going to go look for it.
You were spotted at the scene, too.
Why didn't you find it for me?
The place was completely destroyed.
That tiny earring must
have been destroyed too.
That earring was important to me.
You should know that best of all.
One should be enough.
Anyway, you should
realize the situation.
You killed the client.
Mr. Kanie gave me the wrong target.
It's not my fault.
The result is all that counts!
Then do it yourself!
Don't stay out for too long!
Sawa!
What's up?
Are you okay?
Of course not.
It still hurts.
I have a bald spot and everything.
I'm exhausted.
Come in.
I'll make some coffee.
I prefer tea.
Really strong green tea.
I don't have any.
I brought some.
It's bitter...
It's good!
Sawa...
What?
What will we be
doing ten years from now?
What kind of question is that?
There's only one target.
It's an easy job for you.
You got that, Oburi?
Be on time tonight.
Sawa...
Ten years...
Five years...
Even tomorrow
may never come for us.
All I can do for now
is live life to the fullest.
Your life or even tomorrow's lunch...
No one knows what it'll be.
Akai?
That's right.
...to kill you.
That's why you came here?
You knew that, right?
Get ready.
Your parents were killed by...
...Akai and Kanie.
I know.
...for a long time now.
Promise to come back here.
This guy's a
prosecutor for the DA's office.
He was bribed to ignore the
illegal activities of a big corporation.
He'll be in the last train car in three
minutes, so take care of him there.
He doesn't look like a
government suit type.
Be careful.
I don't want Mr. Akai to fire me just yet.
Who the hell are you?
Don't you know?
Just an ordinary citizen.
Die.
You shitty punk!
You punk!
I'm gonna chop you into pieces!
The one in pieces...
...is you!
Sorry, Mr. Akai.
Oburi, what are you doing?
Don't even try it!
Calm down, okay?
Who the hell was that prosecutor?
A cop from the SWAT team.
Didn't Kanie tell you that?
That guy had a gun...
He tried to kill me!
What do I have to do with that?
I'm going to disappear from your sight.
If you follow me, I'll kill you.
Hold it, hold it.
You promised to do
two more jobs, didn't you?
Do it yourself.
Is Sawa with you?
I'm taking her with me.
I see...
You punk, you caused
me some serious trouble...
What happened?
You!
I thought you died already!
Get away!
Get away from him!
Sawa...
Oburi, hang on!
Hang on!
S-Sawa...
Why are you here?
Can you stand?
I guess...
I'm losing feeling in my left arm...
We'd better take care of you quickly.
Don't move!
Sawa...
Oburi, I won't kill you.
Sawa, thank me.
No, let me go!
No! No!
Stop it!
Kanie, you want to shoot him?
Yeah, I really want to shoot this
punk and splatter his blood all over.
You hear that?
What are you going to do, Sawa?
Oburi, a dog is better
off chained to its master.
Don't...
No...
You didn't have to do
all this just to kill him.
Just killing him isn't enough for me.
You hate him that much?
It's not just that.
It's my hobby.
Hobby?
I really take pleasure in
watching other people's pain.
Nothing else makes me feel like that.
Gross hobby.
Your act really scared me.
I almost thought you'd
betray me for a second...
So, I'll be on my own from now on.
Don't worry.
We already found a
replacement for Oburi.
Where are you going to kill him?
The place where we
made you kill for the first time.
I'm looking forward
to tomorrow's autopsy.
I'm going back.
Why don't you stay tonight?
I have an exam tomorrow.
Why don't you drop out of college?
I look better with
pencils than with guns.
Death caused by massive blood loss.
There are several bullets.
I don't appreciate doing this kind
of stuff first thing in the morning.
We've done most of the
checking before you came in.
Good work.
What's wrong?
This isn't like you...
Did you notice?
What?
I just realized, Mr. Akai...
This place.
It's a parking lot now...
...but this is where that family
got slaughtered a few years ago.
A few years ago...
We did the investigation, you know.
I remember they had a daughter.
She was adopted by somebody.
It was a really sexy girl.
Oburi...
Oburi, I didn't think you
had the balls to kill Kanie.
But in your condition, I
don't think you can beat me.
Right?
This time, I'll nail you myself!
Right now, you don't even
have the strength to pull that trigger!
...not with your left hand.
Sawa?
What's going on, Sawa?
My hand!
You and Oburi...
The one who killed Kanie was me.
Oburi is fine.
The two of you tricked me...
Why?
Do you know how long
I've waited for this moment?
This is for Papa and Mama...
...and for me.
Sawa!
Let's go!
Where the hell were you?
Shut up!
I'm gonna win today!
Go get everybody!
Wait just a little longer...
Pretty soon...
Oburi will be back.